U.S. Emergency Board No. 169 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits 5064
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board No. 169 Transcript of Proceedings and Exhibits
1941-1968
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
U.S. Emergency Board
5064
2 cubic feet
2 linear ft.
Records (documents).
Transcript of proceedings and exhibits of the Emergency Board No. 169. National Railway Labor Conference and Eastern, Western, and Southeastern Carriers Conference Committees.
3115667
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, August 22, 2014
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 07, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Sources; Railroads -- Employees -- Labor unions -- United States -- Sources; United States. Emergency Board No. 169; National Railway Labor Conference (U.S.)--Sources.
3115667
- Executive Order Establishing Emergency Board No. 169, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 1, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 3, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 5, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Investigation of Disputes Between the Carriers Represented by the National Railway Labor Conference and Certain of their Employees Volume 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Shop Employees Wage, Rules and Fringe Benefits Cases Carriers' Exhibit No. 1-2, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Carriers Exhibits No. 3, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 4, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 5-6, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 7-12, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Carriers' Exhibits No. 13-18, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Carriers Exhibits No. 19-21, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Carriers' Exhibit No. 21 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Proposed Report and Recommendations of Emergency Board No. 169, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Employes' Exhibit No. 13 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Employes' Exhibits No. 1- 3, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Employes' Exhibits No. 4-12, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Final Report Drafts 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Final Report, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Report to the President by the Emergency Board No. 169, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Miscellaneous Reports, 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Press Release, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Correspondence, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Railroad Shipcraft Fact-finding Study, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Related Emergency Boards [Folder 1 of 2], 1941-1952 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Related Emergency Boards [Folder 2 of 2], 1954-1961 (Box 2, Folder 14)